# Makiko Vaughan

(404) 374-6059 | makiko.vaughan@gmail.com | Sharpsburg, Georgia

https://www.linkedin.com/in/makiko-vaughan | https://makikovaughan.github.io/Bootstrap-Portfolio/

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Detail-oriented problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full stack Java applications. Interested in attaining a career that will allow me the opportunity to excel in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

W3Schools JavaScript Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 12/2022)

- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Spring Boot

- Spring Data JPA
- Spring Security (JWT)
- Bootstrap
- REST API's
- SQL

- Unit Testing (JUnit, Mockito)
- SOLID OOP Principles
- Dependencies Injection
- Git

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program | August 2022- December 2022

Training Participant (in progress)

- Participating in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application to Heroku

**TSG USA, Inc.** | Peachtree City, Georgia | July 2017 – August 2018 & June 2019 – June 2022 System Testing Engineer

- Created and conducted 100+ test cases for Panasonic Car Audio System (Honda, Toyota, and Mazda)
- Identified possible defects and its source by reading Audio Specification, then reported findings to development team
- Conducted Effectiveness confirmation tests once defects were fixed

**Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp** | Atlanta, Georgia | September 2018 – December 2018 *Training Participant* 

- Participated in a 12-week, 240+ hour Full Stack Flex Web Development that emphasizes handson class room sessions
- Learned the technologies involved in front-end and back-end (MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js, express.is)
- Received "The Most Likely to Startup" and "The Best in Class" for the last group project

#### **EDUCATION**

Keller Graduate School of Management of DeVry University

- Master of Information Systems Management
- Cumulative GPA: 3.80/4.00
- Graduated with Distinction